there's something going on with your photo in the bathroom, be careful, you
hay movida con tu foto en el baño atenta
've blown up my phone with messages,
me habéis reventado el móvil a mensajes
sending me certain people wearing
mandándome a ciertas personas usando con
certain clothes and such.
ciertas prendas de ropa y tal no
Oh really, in a bathroom, in a bathroom, like
Ay de verdad en un baño en un baño como
I used to do that thing in bathrooms, like you know they
hacía yo lo de los baños como sabéis que
always have bathrooms. I've been doing it for
siempre poseen los baños
years, but it's just
Llevo años pero es que me hace una
funny to me because there are people writing on my
gracia porque hay gente escribiendo mi
Instagram like Marta, I don't know what, I upload a
Instagram como Marta no sé qué subo una
photo of my terrace of the views,
foto de mi terraza de las vistas eso lo
Marta does that, like I don't know what I'm saying, but I'm
hace Marta de no sé qué digo pero es que
left, I mean, I'm really laughing now so as
me quedo o sea de verdad me río ya por
not to cry, I say, let's see, I can't do anything,
no llorar digo a ver no puedo hacer nada
then she always has my mirror. I've been
luego siempre posee mi espejo Llevo años
taking pictures of myself in my mirror for years, things like,
sacándome fotos en mi espejo cosas como
people are crazy, I'm not going to
la gente está mal de la cabeza no voy a
comment on
comentar
anything, I'm not going to comment on anything, but
nada no voy a comentar nada pero vamos
basically, I'm 27 seconds into this
básicamente llevo 27 segundos de este
video and there are three and 27 minutes left.
vídeo y faltan tres con 27 minutos